From the joining process to
how much your total payout, commission, etc. will be, do you
get any salary?
How do you earn in business? Here you can do health
insurance, motor insurance,
and non-motor insurance.
We will support you in all three things.
But if you
[Music]
[Praise]
Hello friends,
in this video I am going to share all the information with you on how to become a health insurance agent of IC Lord Company. The
company is very big,
how does the company work, and
what are the benefits for you in joining the company.
From the joining process to how much you will earn in
total payout, commission, etc., do you
get any salary? How do you earn in business?
I am going to tell you all this in this video. So before proceeding further, you have to
subscribe to the channel, share it, and
definitely click the bell icon. Only then will
you keep getting all the latest updates.
My name is Yogendra Verma, I am ISC
Lord Recruitment Manager and my job is to
recruit for health insurance agents. Here we are
from the health department, so our focus
at ICC Lord will mainly be on health.  For
this we do main hiring, let
me tell you for your knowledge that IC Lord
General Insurance Company is one of the best,
being a great company,
work is done in three segments here, here you
can do health insurance, motor insurance
and non-motor insurance as well,
we will support you in all three things
but if you want to take
ICC Lombard code only for doing motor insurance then
we are sorry,
we cannot give you this code, we
give the code only to those people
who want to do health insurance
and want to do secondary general insurance i.e.
want to do motor insurance or non-motor insurance and whoever
applies the code here for health insurance or applies the code in ICICI Lord, it will be
mandatory for them to give the exam, whether you are a life insurance
agent or a health insurance agent, ₹1
exam fee is charged, even if you
are a fresher and want to join health insurance for the first time, want to
join insurance for the first time, even then an
examination fee of ₹1 is charged
here, only after passing the exam you can get the
basic list of
You get this code only after sharing the documents and
after getting the code, it is necessary to do one policy of health insurance for Rs. 15000 in the first month
and it will be mandatory to do 12 policies in a year, only then
this code will continue for you
and here the entire platform
is digital for which there is
no need to go to any branch, for your knowledge let me
tell you that we have more than 500 agents from all over India
working in this working, they are
working in a great way, along with earning and learning, and they
learn everything digitally properly, the company here does
regular training through Zoom meeting, through Microsoft Teams,
which you can learn easily and with this learning you can make a
big empire in this business,
along with active income, you
also get passive income here, which is going to be very great for you,
friends, no matter in which corner of India you are, you
can easily join us in this working on all over India basis,
you will get
whatsapp2 in the total process  It will take 10
to 15 days, so I hope I was able to
give you information and explain it to you, so
please if you have not subscribed to the channel yet,
please subscribe,
share it, comment and
definitely click the bell icon. Hello,
thank you very much for listening to me
[Music]